There's a new spectator in the house, the President of the United States, Donald Trump.
And his granddaughter, Kai, also with him, just arriving to the stands here.
We're walking to the Oval Office now.
My favorite thing of all time.
What's up vlog, welcome back to the channel.
This is a huge vlog.
I am going to Washington DC right now to then go to the Ryder Cup
with my grandpa.
So I'm looking forward to this.
I'm really excited to finally go to the Ryder Cup.
I've never been, but obviously my whole life I've always heard about it.
I've always watched it.
So I'm looking forward to going tomorrow.
I started realizing that I can't really wear like sweatpants anymore on the plane.
I don't know.
I feel like I have to like wear jeans now because I'm older.
Who knows?
That's not like very logical.
This outfit we're rolling with jeans.
and then my Miami shirt.
Alright guys, so I'm in the lounge right now, waiting.
And I ordered a pumpkin spice from the Starbucks across the zone.
I'm looking forward to having my first pumpkin spice of the fall season.
I'm sorry, I got the pumpkin chai spice.
Best drink ever.
Really best drink ever.
Fight me on it.
Pumpkin chai spice is the best drink of all time.
So that's what I'm going to go get in like six minutes or so.
All right guys, I got my drink.
I tried making it low calorie and the low calorie on set does not make
it taste better.
Low key shrimp's got the full calorie.
It's so different now.
My favorite thing of all time is literally this.
Favorite thing of all time.
I don't care what anyone says, favorite thing of all time.
But we'll like see all the syrups on the bottom.
You grab a straw.
What the heck?
That was fun.
How was that?
The flavor, everything.
I'm cleaning right now.
In the car
and go inside to the White House now.
We're walking to the Oval Office now.
This never gets old.
Alright, you guys.
So I literally went to the Oval Office.
I literally hung out with my grandpa while he was just like working.
And then I had dinner with him for like an hour or so.
Now it's like 9.30.
I spent the whole afternoon with him pretty much.
Now I'm finally back in my room.
because we kind of got to wake up early-ish.
I'm going to try some of the gluten-free cookies that they gave me.
Last time they did a very good job.
I'm feeling like the white cookie today.
Follow the packaging.
Bring them.
I need to unpack my bags.
my USA rider cum merch
sick, I'm sick so cool
so I'm gonna wear this
I'm gonna rock with my black pants that I literally wear everywhere I go
I cut my belt and I was thinking about wearing this like blue tank top
just to you know really match the USA vibes My husband has these presidential chocolates,
so good.
Socks, wrong.
I got a pair of socks.
I love getting socks.
You can never have enough socks.
Prove me wrong.
Okay, so two socks.
My makeup bag.
Let's put all this stuff in the bathroom.
I like debating if I should wake up early and work out, or if I
should just be lazy.
My makeup bag.
I still have my sweatpants and my golf bag because it was like hard to
travel with all of this stuff.
Oh look, you might rock the easter roll.
That's what I'm thinking.
That's my style.
I'm gonna get ready for bed now.
Alright, what's up everyone.
It's day two, which is the Ryder Cup day.
So I'm gonna put my retainer in and everything.
But I'm gonna go to the gym, so let's do that.
I'm waiting for the elevator right now.
I'm exhausted, but gotta grind.
I'm gonna just walk the stairs
Alright guys, so now I am back at the warehouse In my room room, go
to the shower because I have to leave in an hour and I decided we're
not gonna show long so I just used my body to puffing wand on my
face and I'm gonna use like wash just to really make sure I got all
the like drainage on my face so I'm going to go over it with my
strainer
Alright guys, let's go and eat real fast before I put my makeup on and
everything else.
Chicken and rice.
Chicken and rice for breakfast in the White House, nothing better.
Me and my grandpa are going to the Red Cup today.
I'm so excited.
I've never been to the Red Cup.
I've always wanted to go.
It's always been like a dream of mine.
So I'm like really happy that I get to go.
But I'm really excited and very thankful that I had the opportunity to go, especially
with my grandpa.
We're gonna have a lot of fun, obviously.
I think we might be walking out Bryson for the the second half, so that's
going to be cool.
Don't quote me on that, though.
We'll see.
I'm really excited to walk through the tunnel as well.
I think walking through the tunnel is going to be so much fun.
So I woke up early.
I went to Lifetime in DC.
I was a little lost, because obviously, normally you go to your gym, you know
where everything is.
It was nice.
I'm gonna do my hair up here.
My hair and makeup done.
Now I am just putting my dirty clothes right here, my shoes on.
I'm gonna wear these to use like golf shoes.
They look cool.
Good shoes.
They're golf shoes too so they kinda add like a little golf touch to
it.
I'm gonna put my laptop in my bag and then we're gonna head out.
So I actually packed a American flag accelerator in my bag.
I have all my stuff in here.
I'm probably gonna end up like not studying but like maybe I'll take a look
at like my stuff.
I also want to get like my jewelry on and stuff.
my watch, my ring
my watch is on my ring is on now let's do the ring that my
mom got me
she's like there's like a lock on mom
okay
oh oh i got it, oh let's go
Let's go ride a car.
USA.
Oh my god, I think that's a helicopter landing right now.
We started the day by heading to the Ryder Cup on Marine One.
The Ryder Cup is a golf tournament held every two years where the best players
from the US and Europe go head to head.
I've always wanted to experience it but getting to go my grandpa made it even
more special.
I'm on the Air Force One now.
It's a very close call.
There's the water
filter!
This is cool!
Here we go, right here
got
it
The
USA!
So, as we get set for the afternoon session, there's a new spectator in the
house, the President of the United States, Donald Trump.
and his granddaughter Kai also with him, just arriving to the stands here
with the United States trailing Europe 3-1.
So we'll see if the president can pull off some sort of comeback here with
the United States trailing 3-1 after just about everything went the European way in the
morning alternate shot session.
Dan Hicks along with Brad Faxon, Paul McGinley, and the rest of our crew getting
set here as we anticipate what should be a very spirited second
session.
the European team swept the Americans two years ago and almost pulled it off again
here before it was Cantlie and Shockley securing the lone point
USA!
Donald Trump!
.
Go, go, go, go!
Storbritannia
Kampioen
You
got it JJ!
You got it JJ!
Stenbergs
Let's go!
All right, so now we're heading back to the White House.
I
had the
best time getting to attend the Ryder Cup for the first time.
This has been a dream of mine for so long, and it was even better
than I expected.
Now we're heading back to the White House and I'm looking forward to playing golf
with Grandpa tomorrow.
I always love coming to visit and getting to spend quality time with him.
I hope you guys enjoyed the rest of the video.
Okay guys, we're back at the White House.
Now we're just hanging out in the Oval Office.
Pretty cool.
Pretty much I am here just chilling outside the Oval Office.
My grandpa is working right now.
And I am just sitting out here.
It's so peaceful.
It's also so nice.
I had the best time of my entire life today.
It was so nice to just be there and support Team USA.
And all the support from the fans and everything was just crazy.
I had a great experience.
And probably one of the coolest things I've ever been to.
I would say that, Ryder Cup, the Masters, then UFC.
But really cool experience.
I had a great time.
And now I'm just feeling it the way I was, just staying outside enjoying it.
It's so beautiful here, and we're obviously so extremely lucky to be here.
Not many people get to come here, and especially have a family member in office,
so it's really, really cool just to be here and soak it all in, because,
you know, one day it won't be here anymore.
So yeah, it's really nice just sitting out here enjoying it.
I'm probably going to grab a Diet Coke, because I'm really thirsty, but tired, thirsty,
worked out this morning, you guys saw that.
Had a great day.
Oh, and Whoop made me a custom made Team USA band.
I'm going to take it off so I can show you guys.
Hold up.
Yeah, Ryder Cup 2025, and then Team USA on the end.
Only Team USA players and some Whoop members had this.
I'm so lucky to have this.
It's awesome.
It also matches my nails.
So cool.
Okay, so my favorite thing of all time is to grab a Diet Coke from
the machine.
Actually, sorry, a root beer from the machine, not Diet Coke.
Let's go.
So grandpa's still meeting, so I'm just chilling in the OVA office, scrolling on TikTok.
That's what I'm doing.
I'm supposed to be studying for my psych work, or AP psych work, but I
have not been doing that.
So I'm kind of just procrastinating.
I promise you, I will study.
But yeah, this is kind of cool.
There's no better place to scroll on TikTok than the OVA office.
I guess I'm finally back after a long day I wore steak to my room
because I'm exhausted and put my pajamas on and I'll be right back I might
save me out oh look at me
yes that looks delicious oh my god can't wait to eat it first
I don't
know what steak this is, but
Looking forward to trying it
Mmm This is just what I needed So good
Sorry
I'm not going to put a lot of makeup on today because I'm just putting
both.
Let's try to get it ready.
so I just grab my bag of all my stretchy stuff
alright guys so now I'm walking to the elevator with my golf clubs on going
downstairs to meet grandpa to go to the golf course with him and play golf
with him
alright so we're just going to meet grandpa now
we're accelerating
He's coming down shortly I think.
So
now we're heading to the range.
um look how sick this course is this course is so cool driving to the
range right now
be careful around the back here all right yeah i'm looking forward to playing
what grandpa obviously today it's gonna be really fun it's kind of cold not really
packed for the cold so a little cold right now but i'm looking forward to
playing this course is honestly sick it's really nice horse yeah it's cold besides that
chilling right now so looking forward to playing
So now I'm going to go to off the first hole.
Do a little warm up and yeah, let's go.
Look how beautiful this course is.
One of the nicest courses I think ever.
all right guys i got par at the first hole um and now now i'm
just like
Oh good, good crossy train.
Look how nice it is.
Pretty pure.
Thank
you.
What did you get?
Is that a birdie or eagle?
Four.
That was a birdie.
We all tied.
Well, I was closer than Kai.
Kai, you have to putt it.
Good birdie.
Wow, four birdies.
Those were two good shots, honey.
Thank you.
Good birdie.
You made three birdies today.
There you
go.
There you go, partner.
Wow.
All right, just finished playing.
Shot one under the front, shot two over the back, so one over, through.
through I think it was it's 6,700 yards so pretty far but you know pretty
proud I'm pretty proud of myself played well and fought hard made a lot of
up and downs and now we're gonna have lunch with grandpa I had a great
time playing with grandpa and now I'm back in the room I am going to
change get ready for the plane and then head back to Florida let's go guys
so this is also my last day here in Bali I did order some oh
look at that that actually looks really good
I can't wait to dig into this.
I'm really hungry.
I got a butter knife for this steak.
Let's see.
I have a butter knife.
So good.
I'm going to enjoy this.
I'll see you guys later.
I
guess I just got
home.
It's like 10 o'clock right now.
I'm really tired.
Long day.
These are dangerous.
I want a bite.
My mom's the best.
I'm always coming home to the best surprises.
I
really regret eating those donuts.
My stomach is so bloated right now because I am gluten free, but it's okay.
It is what it is.
Drinking my White House water.
I'm going to change my clothes, start my load of all my dirty clothes, and
then get to bed and play golf tomorrow morning.
Bye guys.